A Guide to the Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Collection, 1856-2019
Shenandoah County Library
- Series V: Church Membership Records, 1956-2005
  - 38758101567153 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 9)
    - “Pastor Carbaugh Transfers” (1 of 2),1977-1988 (Box-folder 9.12)
    - “Pastor Carbaugh Transfers” (2 of 2),1977-1988 (Box-folder 9.13)
    - Church Baptisms, Funerals, Communion, Confirmation, Weddings, and Transfer Lists, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 9.14)
    - “Pastor Heckathorn Transfers,” 1983-1986 (Box-folder 9.15)
    - “Pastor Murray Transfers,” 1989 (Box-folder 9.16)
    - “Letters of Membership Transfer" (1 of 3), 1992-1997 (Box-folder 9.17)
    - “Letters of Membership Transfer" (2 of 3), 1992-1997 (Box-folder 9.18)
    - “Letters of Membership Transfer" (3 of 3), 1992-1997 (Box-folder 9.19)
    - Active Members List, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 9.20)
    - Confirmed Members, 2000 (Box-folder 9.21)
    - Mt. Zion Membership, 2000 (Box-folder 9.22)
    - Church Roll Update, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 9.23)
  - 38758101567161 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 10)
    - Child Roster, “B” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.1)
    - Child Roster, “C” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.2)
    - Child Roster, “D” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.3)
    - Child Roster, “E” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.4)
    - Child Roster, “F” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.5)
    - Child Roster, “G” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.6)
    - Child Roster, “H” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.7)
    - Child Roster, “K” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.8)
    - Child Roster, “L” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.9)
    - Child Roster, “M” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.10)
    - Child Roster, “N” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.11)
    - Child Roster, “O” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.12)
    - Child Roster, “P” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.13)
    - Child Roster, “R” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.14)
    - Child Roster, “S” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.15)
    - Child Roster, “W” Last Names, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 10.16)
    - Member Card File, “B” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.17)
    - Member Card File, “C” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.18)
    - Member Card File, “D” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.19)
    - Member Card File, “F” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.20)
    - Member Card File, “G” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.21)
    - Member Card File, “H” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.22)
    - Member Card File, “K” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.23)
    - Member Card File, “L" Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.24)
    - Member Card File, “M” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.25)
    - Member Card File, “O” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.26)
    - Member Card File, “P” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.27)
    - Member Card File, “R” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.28)
    - Member Card File, “S” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.29)
    - Member Card File, “W” Last Names, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.30)
    - Member Card File, Transfers and Not Communing, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 10.31)
    - Member Card File, Former and Transferred Members (1 of 2), ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.32)
    - Member Card File, Former and Transferred Members (2 of 2), ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.33)
    - Member Card File, “B” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.34)
    - Member Card File, “C” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.35)
    - Member Card File, “D” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.36)
    - Member Card File, “E” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.37)
    - Member Card File, “F” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.38)
    - Member Card File, “G” Last Names (1 of 2), ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.39)
    - Member Card File, “G” Last Names (2 of 2), ca. 2000 (Box-folder 10.40)
  - 38758101567179 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 11)
    - Member Card File, “H” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.1)
    - Member Card File, “J” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.2)
    - Member Card File, “K” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.3)
    - Member Card File, “L” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.4)
    - Member Card File, “M” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.5)
    - Member Card File, “N” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.6)
    - Member Card File, “O” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.7)
    - Member Card File, “P” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.8)
    - Member Card File, “R” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.9)
    - Member Card File, “S” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.10)
    - Member Card File, “T” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.11)
    - Member Card File, “W” Last Names, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 11.12)
    - Member Card File Labeled “I” (1 of 3), undated (Box-folder 11.13)
    - Member Card File Labeled “I” (2 of 3), undated (Box-folder 11.14)
    - Member Card File Labeled “I” (3 of 3), undated (Box-folder 11.15)
    - Member Card File (1 of 2), undated (Box-folder 11.16)
    - Member Card File (2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 11.17)
- Series VI: Church Records, 1884-2013
  - 38758101567187 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 12)
    - “Mt. Zion Lutheran Congregation: A Century with Christ, A Century of Service, 1884-1984" (Box-folder 12.1)
    - “Mt. Zion Lutheran Church 1884-2009” (Box-folder 12.2)
    - Deeds, 1898-1981 (Box-folder 12.3)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Constitution, February 6 1949 (Box-folder 12.4)
    - Church Constitutions, 1949-1966 (Box-folder 12.5)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Documents, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 12.6)
    - Proposed Budgets, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 12.7)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Reports and Correspondence (1 of 2), 1967-1976 (Box-folder 12.8)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Reports and Correspondence (2 of 2), 1967-1976 (Box-folder 12.9)
    - (Box-folder 12.10)
    - “Windows Stain,” 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12.11)
    - Parish Letters, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 12.12)
    - Mt. Zion Financial Secretary, 1972 (Box-folder 12.13)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Deed and Addition, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 12.14)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Constitution, ca. 1978 (Box-folder 12.15)
    - Proposed Constitutional Changes, ca. 1978 (Box-folder 12.16)
    - “In Remembrance” Church Memorials, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 12.17)
    - “Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Monthly Report,” 1979 (Box-folder 12.18)
    - Vietnamese Refugee Family, 1979 (Box-folder 12.19)
    - Betty Racey, Hung Truong, and Family Scrapbook Items, 1979 (Box-folder 12.20)
    - Monthly Financial Reports, 1979 (Box-folder 12.21)
    - Cash Disbursed (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 12.22)
    - Cash Disbursed (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 12.23)
  - 38758101567195 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 13)
    - “Stained Glass Proposals” (1 of 3), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 13.1)
    - “Stained Glass Proposals” (2 of 3), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 13.2)
    - “Stained Glass Proposals” (3 of 3), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 13.3)
    - Social Hall Construction Letter, September 24 1980 (Box-folder 13.4)
    - Monthly Financial Reports, 1980 (Box-folder 13.5)
    - Church Financial Report, 1980 (Box-folder 13.6)
    - Building Proposal, Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 13.7)
    - “New Addition” Expenses and Gifts, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13.8)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Addition Scrapbook Pages, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13.9)
    - Central Valley Area Mission Strategy, 1981 (Box-folder 13.10)
    - Legal Documents, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 13.11)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church 1982 Budget and Building Fund Repayment Schedule (Box-folder 13.12)
    - Monthly Financial Reports, 1982 (Box-folder 13.13)
    - Financial Reports, 1983 (Box-folder 13.14)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Financial Reports, 1983 (Box-folder 13.15)
    - Church Repair Proposal, February 29 1988 (Box-folder 13.16)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, 1988 Budget (Box-folder 13.17)
    - “First Supplement to the Bulletin of Reports,” Virginia Synod, 1990 (Box-folder 13.18)
    - Homecoming Sunday Brochure, September 1 1996 (Box-folder 13.19)
    - Rev. Murray Ziegenfuss Departure Paperwork, 1998 (Box-folder 13.20)
    - “Recording Secretary’s Report,” 2000 (Box-folder 13.21)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Constitution, ca. 2003 (Box-folder 13.22)
    - Church Archives Team, ca. 2004 (Box-folder 13.23)
    - “Workers for the Clothes Closet,” 2008 (Box-folder 13.24)
    - Breakfast and Dinner Events, 2008-2014 (Box-folder 13.25)
    - Events, ca. 2009 (Box-folder 13.26)
    - 125th Anniversary Planning, 2009 (Box-folder 13.27)
    - Welcome to Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Brochure, Undated (Box-folder 13.28)
    - “Help for Julie,” Undated (Box-folder 13.29)
    - “History of how Mt. Zion Lutheran Church began,” Undated (Box-folder 13.30)
    - Christmas Card from Susan Hepner,Undated (Box-folder 13.31)
  - 38758101567369 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 29)
    - Parochial Reports, 1973-1974+ (Box-folder 29.6)
  - 38758101567591 Map Case Drawer E, Folder 11 (Folder 1)
    - Roanoke College Diploma, Hearicum Franklin Coffelt, June 14 1905
  - 38758101567583 Map Case Drawer E, Folder 12 (Folder 2)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Addition, Architectural and Electrical Drawings, April 1 1980
- Series VII: Women of the Church
  - 38758101567203 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 14)
    - Margurile Reedy Cutler, ca. 1925-2013 (Box-folder 14.1)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women Treasurer’s Book, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 14.2)
    - “The Women’s Missionary Society Minutes,” December 1946-1948 (Box-folder 14.3)
    - “Universal Declaration of Human Rights,” 1949 (Box-folder 14.4)
    - Constitution, Women’s Missionary Society of the United Lutheran Church in America, 1949 (Box-folder 14.5)
    - Mt. Zion Ladies Aid Missionary Society Meeting Minutes, January 1949-April 1953 (Box-folder 14.6)
    - Mt. Zion “Lutheran Church Women’s Treasurers’ Book,” June 1949-1963 (Box-folder 14.7)
    - “The Fruit of the Spirit Our Life in Christ Programs of Worship,” 1951 (Box-folder 14.8)
    - “Pilgrimage into the Reality Programs of Worship,” 1955 (Box-folder 14.9)
    - Mt. Zion Ladies Aid, 1955 (Box-folder 14.10)
    - The United Lutheran Church Women of Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 14.11)
    - United Lutheran Church Women Life Member Card Issued to “Mrs. Wilbur Gochenour,” June 1 1959 (Box-folder 14.12)
    - “Let Us Pray Program of Worship,” 1959 (Box-folder 14.13)
    - “Abide in Me Programs of Worship,” 1960 (Box-folder 14.14)
    - Mt. Zion United Lutheran Church Women Documents, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 14.15)
    - Shenandoah Conference, United Lutheran Church Women, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 14.16)
    - Mt. Zion Ladies Aid Social Ministry, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 14.17)
    - “Rug Cutting,” September 1962 (Box-folder 14.18)
    - “The LCW Guide,” 1965 (Box-folder 14.19)
    - Letter to “Mrs.Copp,” Mt. Zion Lutheran Church from “Garenganze Evangelical Mission,” Democratic Republic of Congo, 1967 (Box-folder 14.20)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Minutes, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 14.21)
    - “Remembering and Renewing,” Lutheran Church Women “10th Birthday” Pamphlet, 1972 (Box-folder 14.22)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women, 1973 (Box-folder 14.23)
    - “L.C.W. Thanksgiving Program, Thanksgiving in America,” November 21 1976 (Box-folder 14.24)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women Yearbook1981 (Box-folder 14.25)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women (1 of 2), 1981-1985 (Box-folder 14.26)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women (2 of 2), 1981-1985 (Box-folder 14.27)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women 1982 Yearbook (Box-folder 14.28)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women 1983 Yearbook (Box-folder 14.29)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women 1984 Yearbook (Box-folder 14.30)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women 1985 Yearbook (Box-folder 14.31)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women (1 of 2), 1986-1990 (Box-folder 14.32)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women (2 of 2), 1986-1990 (Box-folder 14.33)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Yearbook, 1989 (Box-folder 14.34)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Yearbook, 1990 (Box-folder 14.35)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Yearbook, 1991 (Box-folder 14.36)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes (1 of 3), 1991-1995 (Box-folder 14.37)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes (2 of 3), 1991-1995 (Box-folder 14.38)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes (3 of 3), 1991-1995 (Box-folder 14.39)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Yearbook, 1992 (Box-folder 14.40)
    - Certificate of Recognition, Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA from “VSWO Mission Growth,” July 21 1995 (Box-folder 14.41)
    - Service Committee, Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 14.42)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes (1 of 4), 1996-2004 (Box-folder 14.43)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes (2 of 4), 1996-2004 (Box-folder 14.44)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes (3 of 4), 1996-2004 (Box-folder 14.45)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes (4 of 4), 1996-2004 (Box-folder 14.46)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Yearbook, 2004 (Box-folder 14.47)
    - Mt. Zion-Fairview Women of the ELCA Yearbook, 2005 (Box-folder 14.48)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA, 2006 (Box-folder 14.49)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Minutes, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 14.50)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Records, 2009 (Box-folder 14.51)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Handbook, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 14.52)
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Records, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 14.53)
  - 38758101567211 Stack 10, Shelf 2 (Box 15)
    - Mt. Zion Ladies Aid Financial Notebook, 1944-1954
    - Mt. Zion Church Ladies Aid Society Record Book, 1958-1961
    - Mt. Zion Church United Lutheran Church Women Record Book, 1958-1962
    - Ladies Aid of the Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, 1961-1969
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Women Record Book, 1963-1969
    - “A History of the Lutheran Church Women” by Lami Johnson, ca. 1980
    - Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA Records, 1985-1991
- Series VIII: Church Youth, 1919-2013
  - 38758101567229 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 16)
    - Sunday School and Cradle Roll Certificates, 1913-1943 (Box-folder 16.1)
    - “Baby Birthday Book Fairview,” 1927-1951 (Box-folder 16.2)
    - Martha Jane Gochenour “Little Bible Lesson Pictures,” 1943 (Box-folder 16.3)
    - Certificate of Baptism, Donald Wilbur Gochenour, April 6 1944 (Box-folder 16.4)
    - Mary Ann Fravel Sunday School Class Book, ca. 1950 (Box-folder 16.5)
    - William Gochenour “Virginia Week Day Schools” Packet, 1951 (Box-folder 16.6)
    - Linda Jo Fravel Luther League Handbook, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 16.7)
    - “Baby Birthday Book,” 1954-1981 (Box-folder 16.8)
    - Confirmation Classes, 1957-1976 (Box-folder 16.9)
    - Luther League Programs, 1959 (Box-folder 16.10)
    - Sunday School Class Books (1 of 6), ca. 1960 (Box-folder 16.11)
    - Sunday School Class Books (2 of 6), ca. 1960 (Box-folder 16.12)
    - Sunday School Class Books (3 of 6), ca. 1960 (Box-folder 16.13)
    - Sunday School Class Books (4 of 6), ca. 1960 (Box-folder 16.14)
    - Sunday School Class Books (5 of 6), ca. 1960 (Box-folder 16.15)
    - Sunday School Class Books (6 of 6), ca. 1960 (Box-folder 16.16)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (1 of 5), ca. 1962 (Box-folder 16.17)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (2 of 5), ca. 1962 (Box-folder 16.18)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (3 of 5), ca. 1962 (Box-folder 16.19)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (4 of 5), ca. 1962 (Box-folder 16.20)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (5 of 5), ca. 1962 (Box-folder 16.21)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Sunday School Class Books (1 of 2), ca. 1963 (Box-folder 16.22)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Sunday School Class Books (2 of 2), ca. 1963 (Box-folder 16.23)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 16.24)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 16.25)
    - Sunday Church School Secretary’s Record, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16.26)
    - Sunday School Class Register Book (1 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16.27)
    - Sunday School Class Register Book (2 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16.28)
    - Sunday School Class Register Book (3 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16.29)
    - Sunday School Class Register Book (4 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16.30)
    - Sunday School Class Register Book (5 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16.31)
  - 38758101567237 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 17)
    - Sunday Church School Secretary’s Record, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 17.1)
    - “Parish Education Material,” 1966-1969 (Box-folder 17.2)
    - “Bible School,” 1972-1973 (Box-folder 17.3)
    - Sunday School Class Books (1 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17.4)
    - Sunday School Class Books (2 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17.5)
    - Sunday School Class Books (3 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17.6)
    - Sunday School Class Books (1 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.7)
    - Sunday School Class Books (2 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.8)
    - Sunday School Class Books (3 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.9)
    - Sunday School Class Books (4 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.10)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books (1 of 3), September 1979-August 1980 (Box-folder 17.11)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books (2 of 3), September 1979-August 1980 (Box-folder 17.12)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books (3 of 3), September 1979-August 1980 (Box-folder 17.13)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books (1 of 2), September 1980-August 1981 (Box-folder 17.14)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books (2 of 2), September 1980-August 1981 (Box-folder 17.15)
    - Sunday School Monthly Report Sheets, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 17.16)
    - Sunday School Class Books (1 of 3), September 1981-August 1982 (Box-folder 17.17)
    - Sunday School Class Books (2 of 3), September 1981-August 1982 (Box-folder 17.18)
    - Sunday School Class Books (3 of 3), September 1981-August 1982 (Box-folder 17.19)
    - Sunday School Secretary’s Record Book, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 17.20)
  - 38758101567245 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 18)
    - “Baby Birthday Book Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Cradle Roll,” 1981-1993 (Box-folder 18.1)
    - Sunday School Monthly Report Sheets, 1982 (Box-folder 18.2)
    - Sunday School Class Register Books (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 18.3)
    - Sunday School Class Register Books (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 18.4)
    - Sunday School Class Register Book, 1983 (Box-folder 18.5)
    - Monthly Report Sheets, Sunday School, 1983 (Box-folder 18.6)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Books, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 18.7)
    - Sunday School Class Register Books (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 18.8)
    - Sunday School Class Register Books (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 18.9)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Financial Reports, 1984 (Box-folder 18.10)
    - Vacation Bible School, June 17-22 1984 (Box-folder 18.11)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Sunday School Class Record Books (1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 18.12)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Sunday School Class Record Books (2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 18.13)
    - Sunday School Class Books (1 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 18.14)
    - Sunday School Class Books (2 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 18.15)
    - Sunday School Class Books (3 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 18.16)
    - Sunday School Class Register Books, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 18.17)
    - Sunday School Class Record Books (1 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 18.18)
    - Sunday School Class Record Books (2 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 18.19)
    - Sunday School Class Record Books (3 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 18.20)
    - “Baby Birthday Book” Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Cradle Roll, 1995-2010 (Box-folder 18.21)
  - 38758101567252 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 19)
    - “Nursery and Pre-K,” 1999-2002 (Box-folder 19.1)
    - “Class X,” 1999-2002 (Box-folder 19.2)
    - “Upper Elementary, Grades 4-6,” 1999-2002 (Box-folder 19.3)
    - “Class 8,” 1999-2002 (Box-folder 19.4)
    - “Pre-Elementary, Ages 0-5,” 1999-2002> (Box-folder 19.5)
    - “Lower Elementary, Grades 1-3,” 1999-2002 (Box-folder 19.6)
    - “Class 9,” 1999-2002 (Box-folder 19.7)
    - “High School,” 1999-2002 (Box-folder 19.8)
    - Mt. Zion Young Adult Class, ca. 2000 (Box-folder 19.9)
    - Cradle Roll, Children’s Birthdates, 2002-2013 (Box-folder 19.10)
    - Traditional Bible Study Class, 2012 (Box-folder 19.11)
    - Be Truthful Pamphlet, Anna Parsons, undated (Box-folder 19.12)
    - “Thank You, God For…” Booklet, 1980 (Box-folder 19.13)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Sunday School Class Books, undated (Box-folder 19.14)
    - “Massanetta” Pennant, undated (Box-folder 19.15)
    - Sunday School Class Record Books 1 and 2, Class 8, Mr. Catherine Bly, undated (Box-folder 19.16)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (1 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 19.17)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (2 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 19.18)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (3 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 19.19)
    - Mt. Zion Sunday School Class Record Books (4 of 4), Undated (Box-folder 19.20)
  - 38758101567260 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 20)
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1946
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1947
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1948
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1948-1949
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1953
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1954
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1955
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1956
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1957
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1958
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1959
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1959
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1960-1961
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1962
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1962-1965
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1963-1964
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Luther League Record Book, 1963-1965
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1970-1971
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1975-1976
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1977-1978
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1978-1979
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1979-1980
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1980-1981
    - Sunday School Register, 1982-1983
    - Sunday School Register, 1983-1984
    - Sunday School Register, 1984-1985
    - Sunday School Register, 1985-1986
    - Sunday School Register, 1986-1987
    - Sunday School Register, 1987-1988
    - Sunday School Secretary Record, 1991-1992
    - Luther League of America Song Book, Undated
  - 38758101567369 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 29)
    - Billy Gochenour Children’s Record, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 29.1)
    - Mary Ann Fravel Children’s File, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 29.2)
    - Cradle Roll, Children’s Birthdates, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 29.3)
    - Bethany Renee Gochenour Family Resource Folder, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 29.4)
    - Daniel Nicole Cleary Family Resources File, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 29.5)
  - Framed Storage, 38758101567575
    - Cradle Roll, Children’s Birthdates, 1981-1990
- Series IX: Church Books
  - 38758101567286 Stack 10, Shelf 2 (Box 22)
    - Barbara Hamman’s “Prayer’s For Individuals and Families” Book, 1856
    - Mt. Zion Church Book of Worship, 1899
    - Prayer Book Presented to Alice Gochenour, 1904
    - Common Service Book of the Lutheran Church, 1918
    - Services with Music from the Common Service Book of the Lutheran Church, 1918
    - The Parish School Hymnal, 1926
    - Prayer Book Presented to Josiah Fravel, June 10 1928
    - New Testament Present to Lois Fry by Josiah Fravel, December 25 1928
    - Richard and Linda Gochenour’s Luther’s Catechism, 1935
    - Hymns of Christian Service, 1936
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church “The Little Bible,” 1964
    - Landon Walker “Heart Shield Bible” Present by Mt. Zion Sunday School Class, 1944
    - New Testament John Calvin Sager “From Your Sunday School Teacher,” Undated
  - 38758101567294 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 23)
    - Luther’s Small Catechism, Published by Henkel Press, 1867